indianrecruit.in 2018-09-29

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [rohitshra1@gmail.com](mailto:rohitshra1@gmail.com).

### Gathering and Use of Information

Indianrecruit.in will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user’s permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to the Indianrecruit.in Web Site may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i)contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Indianrecruit.in may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, or, on occasion, when mailing lists are made available to other organizations. (The occasional provision of mailing lists to such organizations is the only case where such information would be provided to third parties).

For more information regarding Indianrecruit.in’s policies on the handling and use of Indianrecruit.in’s membership list, please see Indianrecruit.in’s Membership List Policy. The extent of such use is always explained at the time a site visitor provides such information.

If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to ‘opt-out.’ Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to ‘opt-out’ they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed. (For example, if a contest participant elects to ‘opt-out’ on permitting us to collect and use their personal information, we cannot contact them if they win without using such information.)

### Acceptance of these Indianrecruit.in Web Site Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Indianrecruit.in Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

From time to time, Indianrecruit.in may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Indianrecruit.in Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [rohitshra1@gmail.com](mailto:rohitshra1@gmail.com).

###  **Privacy Policy for www.indianrecruit.in**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [rohitshra1@gmail.com](mailto:rohitshra1@gmail.com).

At [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/) and how it is used.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/).  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/) and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.indianrecruit.in](http://www.indianrecruit.in/)‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.  
Privacy Policy Online Approved Site

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Tuesday, March 1st, 2016.
